trustly.com 2012-11-19

# Trustly ®

Effective Date: 03/26/2012

Trustly (owned and operated by Trustly Group AB) is committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity and security of any personal information regarding the people that use our services. This Privacy and Security Policy explains how we protect and use personal information in connection with our service (the "Service") and when you provide it to us on our Web site: www.trustly.com. For purposes of this Policy "Personal information" shall mean information that identifies you, such as your name, personal identity number, phone number, or email address etc.

Trustly has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [support@trustly.com](mailto:support@trustly.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here.](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request) The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site.

## 1\. No sale of Personal information

Trustly will not sell or otherwise assign your Personal information to anyone other than as outlined in this policy. Furthermore, Trustly only uses and discloses your personal information as follows:

1\. to analyze site usage and improve the Service;

2\. to provide you with our Service;

3\. for market research, project planning, troubleshooting problems, detecting and protecting against error, fraud or other criminal activity;

4\. to enforce Trustly’s End User Agreement; and

5\. as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

## 2\. Limitations on the collection and use of Personal Information

From time to time we may request other personal information such as your name, e-mail address and telephone number. If your bank requires you to use your social security number to access your bank account this information will be passed to us as well. We use this information to provide you with the benefits of the Service or to answer any questions you may have regarding our service while visiting our site. In all such instances, you will be given the opportunity to provide or to decline to provide that information, and it will be used only for the stated purpose.

Access to any personal information you provide is strictly restricted and used in accordance with specific internal procedures and safeguard governing access, in order to operate, develop or improve the Service. These individuals have been selected in accordance with our security policies and practices and are bound by confidentiality obligations. They may be subject to discipline, including termination of their employment and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

## 3\. The use of online session information

"Cookies" are alphanumeric identifiers in the form of text files that are inserted and stored by your Web browser on your computer’s hard drive. Trustly may set and access cookies on your computer to track and store preferential information about you. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. Please note that most Internet browsers will allow you to stop cookies from being stored on your computer and to delete cookies stored on your computer. If you choose to eliminate cookies, the full functionality of the Service may be impaired for you.

When you use the Service, we may collect technical and navigational information, such as computer browser type, Internet protocol address and pages visited. This information may be used, for example, to alert you to software compatibility issues, or it may be analyzed to improve the Service.

We may use third party service providers to help us analyze certain online activities using log files. For example, these service providers may help us measure the performance of our online campaigns. We do not share any personal information about our customers with these third party service providers, and these service providers do not collect such information on our behalf. Our third party service providers are required to comply fully with this PrivacyPolicy.

## 4\. Disclosure of your information to protect our rights or if required by law

Trustly reserves the right (and you hereby authorize Trustly) to share or disclose your personal information when Trustly determines, in its sole discretion, that the disclosure of such information is necessary or appropriate:

1\. To prevent prohibited or illegal activities;

2\. To enforce our rights against you or in connection with a breach by you of this Privacy or the End User Agreement; or 

3\. When required by any applicable law, regulation, subpoena or other legal process.

## 5\. Access to personally identifiable information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update it by emailing our Customer Support at [support@trustly.com](mailto:support@trustly.com). We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## 6\. Transfer of Personal Information

Personal information may be transferred to a third party as a result of a sale, acquisition, merger, reorganization or other change of control. If we sell, merge or transfer any part of our business, part of the sale may include your personal information. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

## 7\. Links to other sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Trustly. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

## 8\. Security

We use a combination of encryption techniques firewall barriers, and authentication procedures, among others, to maintain the security of your online session and to protect the Service from unauthorized access.

Our servers are in a secure facility. Our databases are protected from general employee access both physically and logically. We encrypt your Service password so that your password cannot be recovered, even by us. All backup drives and tapes also are encrypted.

We enforce physical access controls to our buildings.

No employee may put any sensitive content on any insecure machine (i.e., nothing can be taken from the database and put on an insecure laptop).

When you enter sensitive information (such as financial information) on our forms we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). This enables client and server applications to communicate in a way that is designed to prevent eavesdropping, tampering and message forgery. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [support@trustly.com](mailto:support@trustly.com).

## 9\. Notification of privacy policy changes

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address submitted to us) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

## 10\. Contact

If you have questions, comments or feedback regarding this Privacy and Security Policy or any other questions, please contact us on [support@trustly.com](mailto:support@trustly.com) or via postal mail at Trustly Group AB, St Göransgatan 63, 112 38 Stockholm, Sweden.
